Rituals, beliefs, and myths in this series are a work of fiction and in no regard refer to religions or faiths of any certain cultures.
A soul binding ritual?
When two souls are bound,
half of a person’s spiritual energy
will flow into the other.
And it will protect you from now on.
You all need to know that in the last stretch
right before we seal it,
the demon will make its last-gasp attempt.
Qi Rong’s strongest power is
his manipulation of fog.
Whatever happens,
we have to continue with the ritual.
What are you standing still for?
When in my battlefield,
everyone must face their worst enemy.
You are…
Who I am
matters no more than who you are.
To get through this door,
you must prove your clairvoyance.
I don’t have time for this.
Now that’s a really good liquor.
A WORTHLESS PUPPET
- Lapdog!
LAPDOG!
We’re locked in here by the demon.
The only way to clear this fog
is to give the demon a sacrifice.
Is your worst enemy
simply these mirrors?
You again?
Alright.
Let’s decide once and for all.
Lapdog!
Scumbag!
Worthless!
Lapdog!
Get out!
Scumbag!
Worthless!
Lapdog!
For the only path to your destination,
you must prove your clairvoyance.
Pete.
Are you serious?
Hell yeah.
Why would I lie?
One of us has to be sacrificed
to lift this fog.
If you won’t do it,
someone else will be sacrificed.
You know damn well how important
they all are to this ritual.
Now choose who will die.
How’d we even choose that?
Would you rather I choose?
Well?
Maybe you?
Or you?
Crap!
I’ll do it.
- Jack.
If it means everyone else gets to live,
I’ll die.
You
who spent his whole life studying heaven.
Do you know
whether heaven is what you observe,
or what observes you?
Heaven
decides the fate of all things.
Heaven is above all things.
Heaven observes us.
We do not observe heaven.
What resides above heaven?
Nothing does.
Fool!
Your eyes study the texts,
but you do not understand the message.
You are not worthy of this eye.
What a shame
that the likes of you are lauded as a seer.
How come when you tell them
to wait for light
they’re always left behind
to die in the dark?
Because no one knows
what heaven has in mind.
All things
are as heaven dictates.
You are not worthy of
the leg that carries you!
Is there no way, Master?
That’s what it shows on the trigrams.
I only tell you what the book says.
Honestly, Master,
have you ever gotten anything right?
Under heaven, you are incompetent
in reading fortunes,
but in this battlefield,
I will grant you the gift of clairvoyance.
Now divine
whether you and your friends
will make it out of this battle alive.
And I will make sure it happens.
What a good liquor.
What the hell is this?
(Life is meaningless.)
(Ideology. Duty.)
(Good. Evil.)
(Nothing is true in the end.)
Lapdog!
Disgrace!
Reconsider your decision
or never call yourself Wu ever again.
Is this all my teaching has led you to?
It was all my fault.
Heaven will always punish
those who are unnatural.
What a disappointment.
It was my fault. I did not teach you well.
Our ancestors gave us one duty;
to protect heaven and nature.
Lapdog!
What does it say?
Will we make it?
The lower trigram is ‘kun.’
The upper trigram is ‘qian.’
The whole hexagram is…
‘Pi.’
What does that mean?
We’re going to fail.
I mean, your prediction
is never accurate anyway, right?
Hey, don’t laugh.
Why did you stop?
You yearn for accuracy, do you not?
I will grant you what you want.
Now divine.
Divine your future.
Otherwise, I will be the one
who decides your fate.
The sound of the drum has gone silent.
Your friends are defeated.
And you are the only one who
has not put up a fight.
Make an effort, you outcast!
Try and find a way out of this.
The harder you try,
the more lost you will be.
So this is your true fate…
To be confined with your
own reflection for all eternity.
At this point, it is undeniable
that what we’re going to do
is nothing short of life-threatening.
If anyone wants to back out now,
just say the word.
If we back out right now,
that means
the demon has already won, doesn’t it?
No.
We will win.
You don’t even dare move your leg
and you think you’ll still find your way out?
I am not here to find a way out.
I am here to seal you.
You think we’re stupid, huh?
And right now, I am waiting,
waiting for my friends
to stand together again.
The last set of divination:
yang has moved into yin.
As dictated by Hexagram 12
changing into Hexagram 45.
The path may begin with difficulties,
but it will end in success.
You haven’t taken a look at the last coin.
I don’t need to look.
Because I’ve seen it.
The clearest I’ve ever seen
in my entire life.
You!
When yang is deterred from earth,
and yin is oppressed,
and a tremendous force
of energy accumulates,
thus is born Earth yao.
When there is too much yin
in a body of water,
and yang is out of balance,
thus is born Water yao.
An abnormally strong storm is often caused by the power of Air and Fire yao.
Don’t you find it strange
that we were taught that yao is unnatural?
But if you look closely at it,
it is, in itself, nature.
You wanna sell that?
The bracelet that seals all yao elementals.
I bet it’ll fetch you a heavy sum.
No.
I’m keeping it.
On this path I chose,
so many backs will turn on me.
But I will always have
the force of nature by my side,
protecting me.
Will you promise me one thing?
Will you try to get the demon
out of my body?
If a solution ever presents itself one day,
I want you to do it.
Why?
You finally learned to live with it now.
More importantly, you have its power.
It’s still a demon.
Pete.
You shouldn’t think of it as a curse.
However it was put inside you,
it was given to you by your parents
to help you overcome your disability,
and to give you a
fair chance at a better life.
You should think of it as a blessing,
and a part of who you are.
Let me give you some advice.
When reading fortunes,
you can’t just be by the book.
You need to read from here.
This is where heaven
communicates with you.
Damn it!
(Heaven favors balances.)
(No matter how powerful a demon is,)
(it cannot be stronger than a human’s will.)
(That’s why demons
make you question your own will.)
(You don’t need to fall for its ploy.)
Pete.
Where’s Niran?
Do you mean to say you’re willing
to be confined here forever?
We can’t keep waiting.
We need to carry on with the ritual.
I’m just scared
that it might defeat me again,
and I’d lose everyone I have.
But you have me now, Pete.
I won’t let that happen.
You know that.
I will never disappear from you.
Blow out the light in front of you.
Put an end to this ritual.
You and I will be free.
Otherwise…
you will be sealed along with me.
No
You will be sealed alone!
As for me,
I’m going back to my friends.
You!
Did you pull me back?
Just as you did.
Everyone’s here now.
You’re the last one to show up.
To think that
I was the only person who got lost.
I didn’t expect that this bond
would really save me.
But you sure learned
how to use its power quickly.
I didn’t learn jack
All I did was think of you
and the thread did its job.
Since our souls are bound to each other,
if you’re ever in trouble again,
why don’t you try thinking of me?
I’ll be there to save you.
You’re not alone, Niran.
You have me.
You have us.
Now…
Are you ready to come back
and defeat this demon?
Storms subsided
Chaos resolved.
The power of evil,
be sealed!
Qi Rong, be sealed!
- Be sealed!
Lord Warrior?
What do you want?
Money?
I’ll give you anything.
10 million?
Will 10 million suffice
I’ll give the first person
who steps out 10 million!
What do I want?
Don’t talk to him!
What I want is my sister’s life spirit back.
And I’ll beat your ass later!
Is that right?
So those Suming bastards
didn’t tell you the truth, then?
What?
Don’t you know
that this ritual you’re performing
won’t simply seal Lord Warrior?
It will suppress all life spirits with him,
including your sister’s!
They lied to you, you fool!
You can’t save your sister, you idiot!
You freaking idiot!
Damn you!
What does he mean, Niran?
Evil General, accept your confinedment!
I’m asking you what he means, Niran!
What does he mean?
Answer me, you jerk!
Let go of me!
Stop, Niran!
Pete!
I said answer me, Niran!
Answer me, you jerk!
Did you lie to me, Niran?
Qi Rong, be sealed!
Let go of me!
Did you lie to me?
Tell me
what Li Puo said wasn’t true.
He was just messing with me, wasn’t he?
He was lying, wasn’t he?
Is my sister safe now?
Answer me!
We might not have saved your sister,
but we’ve saved a thousand more.
I don’t give a damn about that
Why did you lie to me?
Did you lie to me?
What the hell do you take me for?
Shit!
You bastard!
Don’t touch me!
Hey!
What the hell did you do, Niran?
He did not lie to you, Pete.
He lied to us.
Your sister is awake now.
Pete
Ploy
You’re alright now.
You’re safe now.
The demon was sealed once.
Although for a short time,
that still weakened it.
When Niran destroyed the seal,
the life spirits that were sealed alongside it
took this chance when the demon’s weakened to get back to their bodies.
But that means the demon roams free,
and it can grow stronger.
The ongoing political crisis
has no solution in sight.
Get out
DISSOLVE THE PARLIAMENT
The demonstrations all around the country
have been intensified.
SAY NO TO CORRUPTED DEMOCRACY
12 city halls have been set on fire.
FIRE SET BY PROTESTERS
So far, the casualties from this
political turmoil have climbed to 45.
ANALYSTS SUGGEST RESIGNATION WILL NOT RESOLVE CRISIS
I have to be honest.
The situation has officially gotten out of hand.
Even if the Prime Minister resigns now,
I doubt it would stop anything.
Get yourself together
and think about what you did.
We can probably find
another chance to seal it.
You really think so?
You think Li Puo won’t do anything?
How’s your sister?
“The doctor said she can go home
after one more night.”
That’s good.
I know you must be disappointed right now
that your plan fell through.
But thank you
for saving my sister.
I swear I’ll do anything to help you.
I’ll pay you back for this.
Even if I have to die for you,
I’ll do it.
Trust me, Niran.
You really can trust me.
Niran?
Hey!
Niran, what’s wrong?
Shit!
Niran?
Niran!
Hey! What’s wrong?
Niran, wake up
What’s happened
Niran!
May your life spirit drift away
and be lost for all eternity,
Niran.
I’ll save you, Niran.
I’ll make good on that promise.
The doctors ran all the tests they could.
But they didn’t find anything
wrong with him.
Then what happened to him?
He’s just like my sister
when she was unconscious.
What I know is that…
The human soul is separated
into two parts:
First is the life spirit,
which represents yang.
This connects with your core,
intelligence,
personality, and life purpose.
The yin and yang parts of the soul
are generally always intertwined.
But now that Niran’s life spirit
is severed from his soul…
He’s left with the yin part of the soul,
which controls the body.
It’s exactly what happened to Ploy, Pete.
If Ploy could come back,
Niran can, too.
I don’t think it compares.
Your sister’s life spirit was
devoured by Qi Rong.
That was why it could not
return to the body.
But when the demon was weakened,
the life spirits were released,
and they could return to their bodies.
As for Niran
He was attacked by
a life spirit-cutting ritual.
A life spirit-cutting ritual?
Niran’s life spirit has
drifted away from his body,
floating aimlessly around
in the Life Spirit Realm.
Can we at least perform
a ritual to beckon it back?
The Life Spirit Realm is much greater
and more limitless than ours.
Even if we beckon it,
it doesn’t guarantee that he will hear us.
Is there really no way?
Are we supposed to just
leave Niran like this?
There has to be a way to bring him back.
There is.
But the only person who can save Niran
is you.
The silver lining in this situation is that
Niran’s soul is bound to yours.
We can use that connection as a path
to trace Niran’s life spirit.
Only that…
You have to look for him
in the Life Spirit Realm.
You mean he must detach
his own life spirit?
But that is extremely dangerous.
That’s why I’m asking you, Pete,
if you’re willing to risk your life for this.
Yes.
Pete.
It really is dangerous.
Niran is like this because
he saved my sister.
Whatever I have to go up against
or what I have to risk,
I’ll get Niran back.
I’ll do it.
It’s not that I didn’t know what
the soul binding ritual entails.
You think I should just let
the demon devour you like that?
It’s because of you.
Oh?
You made me like this.
The hell, man?
Why are you blaming me?
If we weren’t friends in the first place,
I wouldn’t have to care about you so much.
I see.
So you’re saying I’ve made
your heart feel again?
Ew!
What the hell are you saying?
Well.
You used to be so heartless.
But you’re not anymore.
You care about your friends.
You actually give a damn about people.
See?
This is all my doing.
Huh.
Don’t look so proud of yourself.
But I’ll say…
You’re never heartless from the beginning.
You’re just a tsundere.
You jerk.
See? You’re doing it again.
I’m not a tsundere
You are. You’re being a tsundere right now!
You idiot.
You’re still doing it.
I’m not a tsundere.
You are, too.
This is just my face.
This is how I look, you jerk.
Exactly something a tsundere would say.
You should knock it off.
Shut your mouth and eat your vegetables.
The Life Spirit Realm is vast
and moves as fast as one’s thought
Niran is lost in that world.
When you find him,
you must do whatever it takes
to make him trust you.
Do I know you?
It’s me, Pete.
I don’t know you!
Shit!
Outta my way!
You have only eight hours in that realm.
Otherwise, you won’t be able
to leave forever.
Come back with me.
Come back to your real life.